(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-22T02:20:33.089845",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
hololive production COUNTDOWN LIVE 2022 ▷ 2023 - hololive side -
袋に詰められたナッツのような世間では
In this world like nuts packed in a bag,
誰もがそれぞれ出会った誰かと寄り添い合ってる
Everyone is snuggling up to someone they met.
そこに紛れ込んだ僕らはピーナッツみたいに
We are mixed in there like peanuts,
木の果実のフリをしながら微笑み浮かべる
smiling while pretending to be tree fruits.
幸せのテンプレートの上 文字通り絵に描いたウワベの裏
On the template of happiness, behind the picturesque surface,
テーブルを囲み手を合わせるその時さえ ありのままではいられないまま
Even when sitting around a table putting hands together, we can't be as we are.
隠し事だらけ 継ぎ接ぎだらけのhome you know
A home full of secrets and patches, you know?
噛み砕いてもなくならない 本音が歯に挟まったまま
Even chewed up, real feelings remain stuck in my teeth.
不安だらけ 成り行き任せのlife and I know
Full of anxiety, leaving life to chance, and I know,
仮初めだけの日常だけど
it's just a fleeting everyday life, but...
はしゃぎすぎた週末のシワ寄せならば
Even if it's just the wear and tear
まだ良いのに
of a weekend spent partying too hard...
変わり映えない 外れない 心に付いた足枷
Unchanging, unshakable shackles on my heart.
先の見えない夜の帰り道 「明日なんてなくちゃ良いのに」
On a night home with no end in sight, "It'd be fine if tomorrow never came."
わけのわからないひとつぶのナッツみたいに
Like a single nut of unknown origin,
世間から一瞬で弾き出されてしまう そんなとここそ
Thrown out of society in a single moment.
まがりなりでよかったら傍にいざなって
If mediocrity is fine, invite me by your side.
ともにいられ揺らめき踏んでも割れないからみたいにだから
Even if we sway and stumble together, it won't break.
生まれた場所がキノコの上か地面の中かそれだけの違い
The only difference is whether you were born underground or on a mushroom.
許されないほどにドライなこの世界を等しく雨が湿らせますように
May the rain equally moisten a world too driven to be forgiven.
ときに冷たくて騒がしい窓の向こう you know
Cold and noisy on the other side of the window, you know.
星のひとつも見つからない 見えない耳たぶがあってもいい
Even if there's not a single star, or an invisible earlobe.
ミスだらけアドリブまかせのショーパレードの
A show parade full of mistakes and ad-libs.
所詮はひとだけの日常だから 腹の中にもでも流してねようお
After all, it's just human daily life, so let it flow through your heart.
隠しごとだらけ つぎはぎだらけのホーム you know
A home full of secrets and patches, you know.
とっておきもできないも 残さずに全部喰らいながら
Swallowing everything down without leaving any special treats.
普通などない 正解などない ライフの おお
There's no such thing as normal, no correct answer, life...
狩りすぎまみれの日常だけど ここに僕がいて
Even in a daily life overflowing with hunting, I am here,
あなたがいる この真実だけでも 歪みも垂れてゆく
With just this truth that you are here, distortions start to fade away.
このひとつかみの奇跡を 噛み締めてゆく
Savoring this handful of miracles.
ああ ちょっと君に伝えたい 何かがあったような
Ah, I have something I want to tell you, like something happened.
けっせい まかさの踊るベース 逆様が苦して
Upside down and suffering in a decisive, dancing bass.
恋とは見惑の狂うらむ たださしずめここから行き着くわ
Love is bewitching, mad and resentful, just ultimately leading from here.
アイデンティティ それは思考のアイデンティティ
Identity, that's the identity of thought.
アイデンティティ うなれ君一人のさあ
Identity, howl, you all alone, now!
まだ捨てないで待って それはひとつふたつのディスティニー
Don't throw it away yet, wait, that's one or two destinies.
つなげてハッピー 落ちる流れ星と歪みなあの星
Connecting happy, falling shooting stars and distorted stars.
重なる面影に寄り添う そっと君に寄り添う
Nestling close to overlapping shadows, softly nestling close to you.
弾けだす視界 胸に飛び込むハート 光るあなたのアイデンティティ
A bursting field of vision, a leaping heart, your glowing identity.
難儀プライド 飛び込めデンジャラス さっと羽ばたく 強気な狂気と
Difficult pride, dive into dangerous, quickly fluttering with strong-willed madness.
裏切りお涙頂戴 ランバララ to足取りデンジャラス
Tears for betrayal, run-ba-ra-ra, stepping dangerously.
背後隠れた二人に見るフォーカス やっと見つけた不思議の正体
Focus on the two hidden behind, finally finding the mystery's true identity.
きっと恋とは真逆のプログラム ただ差し止め ここから行き着くわ
Surely love is the exact opposite program, just ultimately leading from here.
アイデンティティ それは希望のアイデンティティ
Identity, that's the identity of hope.
アイデンティティ うなれ君一人のさあ
Identity, howl, you all alone, now!
まだ捨てないで待って それはひとつふたつのディスティニー
Don't throw it away yet, wait, that's one or two destinies.
つなげてハッピー 落ちる流れ星と歪みなあの星
Connecting happy, falling shooting stars and distorted stars.
重なる面影に寄り添う そっと君に寄り添う
Nestling close to overlapping shadows, softly nestling close to you.
弾けだす視界 胸に飛び込むハート 刻むあなたのアイデンティティ
A bursting field of vision, a leaping heart, etching your identity.
悲しみは笑いましょう
Let's laugh away the sadness,
生きるってマリオネット
Living like a marionette,
心臓がスイングしたら
Once your heart starts to swing,
琴線は如何が？
How do your heartstrings feel?
1・2・2・1・2・2 1・2・2・3
1, 2, 2, 1, 2, 2 / 1, 2, 2, 3
私うまく踊れないわ
I can't dance very well,
痛みも 恨みも 悲しみも
Pain, resentment, and sorrow too,
混ぜて 混ぜて こねて こねて
Mix them, mix them, knead them, knead them,
おやすみのキス
A kiss before going to sleep.
Shall we dance? 踊りましょう
Shall we dance? Let's dance,
絶望 欲望 this is the life!
Despair, desire, this is the life!
shadow life!
余計なこと考えしないで ひとつになりましょう
Without thinking about unnecessary things, let's become one.
いいな いいな いいな いいな 人間って 人間って
So nice, being human is wonderful.
いいな
Wonderful.
泣きたいのに笑えちゃう
Even when I want to cry, I find myself smiling,
人生ってピエロ
Life is like a pierrot.
本当の心隠して
Hiding my true feelings,
笑うフリをするの
I put on a smiling face.
1・2・2・1・2・2 1・2・2・3
1, 2, 2, 1, 2, 2 / 1, 2, 2, 3
私うまく生きれないわ
I can't live very smoothly,
本音も ウソも 不安も
My true thoughts, lies, and anxiety,
溶かして 溶かして 蓋して 蓋して
Dissolve them, cover them up,
おやすみなさい
Good night.
Shall we dream? 夢見ましょう
Shall we dream? Let's dream,
寝ても 覚めてても this is the life!
Sleeping or waking, this is the life!
shadow life!
目を閉じて いやなこと ぜんぶ ぜんぶ忘れましょう
Close your eyes and forget all the bad things.
Shall we dance? 不器用でも
Shall we dance? Even if clumsy,
あがいて もがいて this is the life! shadow step?
Struggling through, this is the life! Shadow step?
余計なこと考えしないで ステップを踏み鳴らせ！
Without thinking, make your steps ring out!
Shall we smile? 今 だけ は
Shall we smile? Just for now,
一緒に 笑って みませんか
Won't you smile along with me?
Shadow dance! 今 だけ は 全部 忘れて
Shadow dance! Just for now, forget everything
一緒に 飛びましょう (show!)
And let's jump together!
Shall we dance? 踊りましょう
Shall we dance? Let's dance,
絶望 欲望 this is the life!
Despair, desire, this is the life!
shadow life!
余計なこと考えしないで ひとつになりましょう
Without thinking about unnecessary things, let's become one.
いいな いいな いいな いいな 人間って
So nice, being human...
人間って いいな
Being human is wonderful.
いいな いいな いいな いいな
So nice, so nice...
人間って 人間って いいな
Being human is truly wonderful.
チャン × チェン 逢！！ チキチキバンバン
Chance, chance! Ai! Chiki chiki ban ban
哀！？ チキチキ チャン チェン
Ai!? Chiki chiki chan chan
呼呼！ チキチキバンバン
Ah! Chiki chiki ban ban
愛！！ チュキチュキチュキ バンバン
Ai!! Chuki chuki chuki ban ban
チャン×チャン
Chance × Chance
逢！！チキチキバンバン
Meet! Chitty Chitty Bang Bang!
哀！？チキチキチャンチャン
Alas?! Chitty Chitty Chance Chance
唹呼！チキチキバンバン
Ah! Chitty Chitty Bang Bang
愛！！チュキチュキチュキバンバン
Love!! Choki Choki Choki Bang Bang
HIGH チキチキバンバン
HIGH Chitty Chitty Bang Bang
哀！？チキチキチャンチャン
Alas?! Chitty Chitty Chance Chance
唹呼！チキチキバンバン
Ah! Chitty Chitty Bang Bang
愛！！チュキチュキ
Love!! Choki Choki
猫も杓子も みんな気まぐれで辛い
Even cats and dogs are so fickle and it's tough
酔えばテキーラ あらぬ妄想連鎖でピカァァーン
Get drunk on tequila, wild delusions flash bright
夢はパンドラ ほら開きたくなる
Dreams are like Pandora's box, you just want to open them
みんな期待してピリピアーイ
Everyone, expect it, party people!
決戦は週末の宿命
The decisive battle is the weekend's destiny
チャン×チャン
Chance × Chance
逢！！チキチキバンバン
Meet! Chitty Chitty Bang Bang!
何も勿体ぶらず楽しめフィーバーナイト
Don't hold back, enjoy it, fever tonight!
チャン×チャン
Chance × Chance
哀！？チキチキバンバン！
Alas?! Chitty Chitty Bang Bang!
何度ムシャクシャしたってパーリートナイト
No matter how frustrated you feel, party tonight!
チャン×チャン
Chance × Chance
唹呼！チキチキバンバン
Ah! Chitty Chitty Bang Bang
愚か者ほどhighと化す完全社会
A perfect society where the more foolish you are, the higher you get
チャン×チャン
Chance × Chance
愛！！チキチキバンバン
Love!! Chitty Chitty Bang Bang
みんなスーパースターの卵さディーバーナイト
Everyone's an egg of a superstar, diva tonight!
チャン×チャン
Chance × Chance
逢！！チキチキバンバン
Meet! Chitty Chitty Bang Bang!
何も勿体ぶらず楽しめフィーバーナイト
Don't hold back, enjoy it, fever tonight!
Chance × Chance
哀！？チキチキバンバン！
Alas?! Chitty Chitty Bang Bang!
何度ムシャクシャしたってパーリートナイト
No matter how frustrated you feel, party tonight!
チャン×チャン
Chance × Chance
唹呼！チキチキバンバン
Ah! Chitty Chitty Bang Bang
愚か者ほどhighと化す完全社会
A perfect society where the more foolish you are, the higher you get
チャン×チャン
Chance × Chance
愛！！チキチキバンバン
Love!! Chitty Chitty Bang Bang
みんなスーパースターの卵さディーバーナイト
Everyone's an egg of a superstar, diva tonight!
チャン×チャン
Chance × Chance
逢！！チキチキバンバン
Meet! Chitty Chitty Bang Bang!
何も勿体ぶらず楽しめフィーバーナイト
Don't hold back, enjoy it, fever tonight!
Chance × Chance
哀！？チキチキバンバン！
Alas?! Chitty Chitty Bang Bang!
何度ムシャクシャしたってパーリートナイト
No matter how frustrated you feel, party tonight!
チャン×チャン
Chance × Chance
唹呼！チキチキバンバン
Ah! Chitty Chitty Bang Bang
愚か者ほどhighと化す完全社会
A perfect society where the more foolish you are, the higher you get
チャン×チャン
Chance × Chance
愛！！チキチキバンバン
Love!! Chitty Chitty Bang Bang
みんなスーパースターの卵さディーバーナイト
Everyone's an egg of a superstar, diva tonight!
プラスアイグラマーイシナイ
Plus I grammar is not my thing
でももだけでもみないいらないヘンザッ
Even so, I don't need things I don't need right now
ニイニイリリンシナイジャパニーズプリティイザカヤハフトオ
Japanese purity, let's make the night deeper!
クレイジークラッシュシタイ
Crash, crash, I want to crash!
飲めばノリノリ明け透かしてセズイェー
Drinking makes me wild, I just can't keep my cool!
ブーストバオステージャン夢巻きシマムアツクダンシングオイェー
Boost the bounce on stage, oh yeah!
少しさどうして臆病をかじんだエネルギーを燃たせ千本テキラ
If you turn a blind eye and act like a coward, you'll miss out on the energy!
インキジラメンインフレシタマインダラダラクルマニエンディングジンセイ
Inquiring minds, inflated minds, rolling on down to an ending life!
ミライワナックスシャイニングキドウハリキリニクサソウリュクセイ
Future is now, shining tracks, breaking through like a meteor!
Oh baby一歩近づきにハハハハイ一歩キラー
Oh baby, one step closer to death, hahaha! That's killing it!
まいだけ剥いていいでしょ燃え盛っチャッテいいでしょ
You can just bare it all, right? You can just burn it up, right?
もう少しベイビーオンもう少しベイビーオンアソボクルケルピゲンワトウダイ
Moving a bit, swaying a bit, we're climbing up that mountain!
ハラハラ時間にスポットアタナナイツマデドキドキハチジカン
Focusing on the moment, forever and ever thrilled!
チャン×チャン
Chance × Chance
逢！！チキチキバンバン
Meet! Chitty Chitty Bang Bang!
何も勿体ぶらず楽しめフィーバーナイト
Don't hold back, enjoy it, fever tonight!
Chance × Chance
哀！？チキチキバンバン！
Alas?! Chitty Chitty Bang Bang!
何度ムシャクシャしたってパーリートナイト
No matter how frustrated you feel, party tonight!
チャン×チャン
Chance × Chance
唹呼！チキチキバンバン
Ah! Chitty Chitty Bang Bang
愚か者ほどhighと化す完全社会
A perfect society where the more foolish you are, the higher you get
チャン×チャン
Chance × Chance
愛！！チキチキバンバン
Love!! Chitty Chitty Bang Bang
みんなスーパースターの卵さディーバーナイト
Everyone's an egg of a superstar, diva tonight!
チャン×チャン
Chance × Chance
逢！！チキチキバンバン
Meet! Chitty Chitty Bang Bang!
何も勿体ぶらず楽しめフィーバーナイト
Don't hold back, enjoy it, fever tonight!
Chance × Chance
哀！？チキチキバンバン！
Alas?! Chitty Chitty Bang Bang!
何度ムシャクシャしたってパーリートナイト
No matter how frustrated you feel, party tonight!
チャン×チャン
Chance × Chance
唹呼！チキチキバンバン
Ah! Chitty Chitty Bang Bang
愚か者ほどhighと化す完全社会
A perfect society where the more foolish you are, the higher you get
チャン×チャン
Chance × Chance
愛！！チキチキバンバン
Love!! Chitty Chitty Bang Bang
みんなスーパースターの卵さディーバーナイト
Everyone's an egg of a superstar, diva tonight!
チャン×チャン
Chance × Chance
逢！！チキチキバンバン
Meet! Chitty Chitty Bang Bang!
何も勿体ぶらず楽しめフィーバーナイト
Don't hold back, enjoy it, fever tonight!
Chance × Chance
哀！？チキチキバンバン！
Alas?! Chitty Chitty Bang Bang!
何度ムシャクシャしたってパーリートナイト
No matter how frustrated you feel, party tonight!
チャン×チャン
Chance × Chance
唹呼！チキチキバンバン
Ah! Chitty Chitty Bang Bang
愚か者ほどhighと化す完全社会
A perfect society where the more foolish you are, the higher you get
チャン×チャン
Chance × Chance
愛！！チキチキバンバン
Love!! Chitty Chitty Bang Bang
みんなスーパースターの卵さディーバーナイト
Everyone's an egg of a superstar, diva tonight!
剥がれ落ちたメイク すっぴんのアニマル
The mask comes off and the beast comes out, barefaced animal
醜くてもやっちゃうのよ
I do it wild even if it's ugly
おすわりとかできない だって待てでもできない
I can't sit, I can't even stay
喉鳴らして いっちゃうまで
Purr until I go
がぶっとしてよっか 高まるビート
You want me to bite you? Accelerating beat
良いも悪いも全然しよ
Let's do both the good and bad
ハマってみよっか 突破するゲート
Let's get lost in each other, plunge into the gate
愛に期待は禁物だよ
High expectations of love is not allowed
ねぇ止まらないほどに狂いたい
I want to get crazy to the point that we can't stop
心真っ赤にしてどうしちゃったのよ
Why is your heart blushing?
痛みすらも愛せたら あたしは幸せです
If I could even love pain, I would be so happy
剥がれ落ちたメイク すっぴんのアニマル
The mask comes off and the beast comes out, barefaced animal
醜くてもやっちゃうのよ
I do it wild even if it's ugly
おすわりとかできない だって待てでもできない 喉鳴らして いっちゃうまで
I can't sit, I can't even stay, purr until I go
牙を出し叫べ ずっきゅんだ
Show your fangs and howl, are you ready?
あたしは噛み付いたら離さないにゃ
Once I bite I don't let go
剥がれ落ちたメイク すっぴんのアニマル
The mask comes off and the beast comes out, barefaced animal
醜くてもやっちゃうのよ
I do it wild even if it's ugly
あがっちゃってよ まわっちゃってよ
Why don't you get high, why don't you go crazy?
めぐっちゃってよ んあーーははは
Why don't we do it more, hahaha
いやいや噛み合い 甲斐なくてつまらない
You can't be serious, so not worth eating to the point it's boring
せめてちょっと拒んでほしかったな
I wanted you to resist at least a little
少しだけ欲張れるなら あたしは幸せになりたいの
If you can be a little greedy, I want to be happy
剥がれ落ちたメイク すっぴんのアニマル
The mask comes off and the beast comes out, barefaced animal
醜くてもやっちゃうのよ
I do it wild even if it's ugly
おすわりとかできない だって待てでもできない 喉鳴らして いっちゃうまで
I can't sit, I can't even stay, purr until I go
あかっちゃってよ くるっちゃってよ
Go crazy, lose your mind, let loose!
なぐっちゃってよ んあーーははは
Let it out, go wild!
あかっちゃってよ くるっちゃってよ
Go crazy, lose your mind, let loose!
なぐっちゃってよ んあーーははは
Let it out, go wild!
やだやだ壊したい なんだか切ない
If you want me to stay by your side forever, it's boring
せめてずっと傍で抱きしめて欲しかったな
I want you to hold me tight and never let go
少しだけ優しくされるなら
If you're going to treat me well just a little bit...
あたしは幸せになりたいの
I want to become happy!
剥がれ落ちたメイク すっぴんの動物
Stripped-off makeup, a bare-faced animal,
醜くてもやっちゃうのよ
even if it's ugly, I'm gonna do it.
おすわりとかできない だって待てでもできない
Can't sit, can't even stay,
喉鳴らして いっいちゃうまで
purring until I go crazy.
ぶっすりとしようか 高まるビート
Let's get blunt, the beat is rising,
良いも悪いも全然しよ
good or bad, let's do it all.
ハマってみよっか 突破するゲート
Let's get hooked, breaking through the gate,
愛に期待は禁物だよ
expectations in love are forbidden.
ねえ止められないほどに狂いたい
Hey, I want to go crazy to the point of no stopping,
心真っ赤にしてどうしちゃったのよ
making my heart crimson, what has happened to me?
痛みすらももし愛せたら
If I could love even the pain,
あたしは幸せです
I would be happy.
だいしきゅーだいしゅき
Dai-shikyu dai-shuki
わっ ちゅー げっ ちゅー 熱烈 ううん ちゅー
What chu get chu, passionate ooh un chu,
しゅきしゅぎて弾けた vivid マインド
a vivid mind that popped from loving too much.
ルーレット グッドスタート きっとゲット
Roulette, good start, surely get,
1等！1等！1等！
first place! First place! First place!
永久センセーション ときめき knock you
Eternal sensation, heart-pounding knock you,
1ミリの隙間にダイビング
diving into a 1-millimeter gap.
ラブスタンプ 全部コンプ 運勢アップ
Love stamp, collect all, fortune up,
いいぞ！いいぞ！いいぞ！いいぞ！
All right! All right! All right! All right!
だって今日はゴッドメンタル
Because today I have god-tier mental,
勇ましきチャレンジャー
a valiant challenger.
ちょっとだけセンチメンタル
Just a little bit sentimental,
だいしきゅー だいしきゅー ♡ 123 ハイ！
dai-shikyu dai-shuki ♡ 1, 2, 3, high!
まみむめもめも目も見れないの
I can't even look you in the eye,
立ちつてとてとて手と手が触れて
our hands touch,
だいしきゅー だいしきゅーになれ！
become dai-shikyu dai-shuki!
もっとキュキュッ キュッ キュート 強制ラブ！
More kyu-kyu, kyu, kyu, cute, forced love!
あのね クリオネ 透けてるハート
Hey, clione, a transparent heart,
でもね この胸 見透かさないで
but hey, don't see right through this chest.
だいしきゅー だいしきゅーになれ！
Become dai-shikyu dai-shuki!
アタシじゃないなんて終わってんね
Saying it's not me is so over.
わっ ちゅー げっ ちゅー 熱烈 ううん ちゅー
What chu get chu, passionate ooh un chu,
しゅきしゅぎて弾けた vivid マインド
a vivid mind that popped from loving too much.
ルーレット ちょっとストップ 一旦休憩
Roulette, a little stop, temporary break,
いやいやいやでもせーの！
no, no, no, but ready, go!
だって今日は求めてる
Because today I'm seeking
麗しきチャレンジャー
a beautiful challenger.
ハート描いたオートメーション
An automation drawing a heart,
だいしきゅー だいしきゅー ♡ 123 ハイ！
dai-shikyu dai-shuki ♡ 1, 2, 3, high!
まみむめろめろにして欲しいの
I want you to melt me,
なにぬねこねこ恋のコネクト
love connection.
だいしきゅー だいしきゅーになれ！
Become dai-shikyu dai-shuki!
もっとキッキッ キッ キッシュー強制ラブ！
More forced love!
あのね マリオネット アヤツラレレイディ
Hey, marionette, a manipulated lady,
でもね それもね 悪くはないね
but hey, even that's not so bad.
だいしきゅー だいしきゅーになれ！
Become dai-shikyu dai-shuki!
アタシじゃないなんて終わってんね
Saying it's not me is so over.
ほれんどに 魔法にして
Turn it into magic,
周波数を見出さないで
don't find the frequency.
誘惑の 魅惑のリップ
The seductive, fascinating lips,
リアルになる be love
becoming real, be love.
まみむめもめもめも眠れないの
I can't sleep,
立ちつてとてとてと手が触れて
hands touching.
だいしきゅー だいしきゅーになれ！
Become dai-shikyu dai-shuki!
もっとキュキュッ キュッ キュッと強制ラブ！
More kyu-kyu, cute, forced love!
あのね クリオネ 透けてるハート
Hey, clione, a transparent heart,
でもね この胸 見透かさないで
but hey, don't see right through this chest.
だいしきゅー だいしきゅーになれ！
Become dai-shikyu dai-shuki!
アタシじゃないなんて終わってんね
Saying it's not me is so over.
終わってんね！
It's so over!
パクっとしたいわ 端から端まで結ばれたいな
I want to go paku, tied from end to end,
パクっとしたいわ 指先と言葉で伝えたいな
I want to go paku, convey with fingers and words,
パクっとしたいわ ワガママかもしれないアンサーで
I want to go paku, with a selfish answer maybe,
パクっとしたいわ どっちもどっちにしたいな
I want to go paku, make both sides mutual,
ただただ問答 間違ってんのはどっち？
Just QA, which one is wrong?
パクっとしたいわ
I want to snap it up!
端から端まで結ばれたいな
Bound tightly from end to end.
パクっとしたいわ
I want to snap it up!
指先と言葉で伝えたいな
Told through fingertips and words.
パクっとしたいわ
I want to snap it up!
ワガママかもしれないアンサーで
With a possibly selfish answer.
パクっとしたいわ
I want to snap it up!
どっちもどっちにしたいな
Wanting both sides to be equal.
ただただ問答
Just endless questioning,
間違ってんのはどっち？ え？
which one is wrong? Huh?
スマイルは0円です
Smiles are free of charge,
でも心はすり減ってくようでさ
but my heart seems to be wearing down.
ああ、満身創痍意気消沈 ローリングサンダー 頑執moving
Battered, disheartened, rolling thunder, moving on!
ドーランペインティング 本当のフェイスに誰が気付いてんだ
Stage makeup—who notices the real face beneath?
冗談めいた言葉で 案外本気です って
Saying "I'm actually serious" in a joking tone,
歌ってそう言うもんでしょって ネットの掲示板で読んだよ
I read online songs are supposed to be like that.
腐ってる日常 なんとか生きててそうかも知れない
Living somehow through a rotting daily life, maybe so.
どうかと思うけど これが私？ ああ言えばこう言う？
I wonder, but is this me? Always having a comeback?
パクっとしたいわ
I want to snap it up!
端から端まで結ばれたいな
Bound tightly from end to end.
パクっとしたいわ
I want to snap it up!
指先と言葉で伝えたいな
Told through fingertips and words.
パクっとしたいわ
I want to snap it up!
ワガママかもしれないアンサーで
With a possibly selfish answer.
パクっとしたいわ
I want to snap it up!
どっちもどっちにしたいな
Wanting both sides to be equal.
繰り出すハリセンで連打連打
Striking repeatedly with a paper fan,
身動き取れないな怠惰怠惰怠惰
unable to move, sheer laziness.
it doesn't matter マナー違反と
It doesn't matter, bad manners and
ディスコミュニケーションと無礼講だ
miscommunication and a free-for-all.
ああ、全くないなバケーション 完全ルーティン
Ah, absolutely no vacation, a complete routine!
本生絞りの柑橘系 want this なんです 気抜いたら9％です
Fresh-squeezed citrus, I want this—9% if you let go.
そう言い聞かされたって終わらない問題です
Even when told that, it's an endless problem.
っつーか実感も伴って終わってる現在進行形かも
Feeling it too, maybe it's an ongoing collapse.
フラットな感情 どっかに行っちゃった
Flat emotions went somewhere away.
宝物はなに？ 捨てるつもりもないのにさ？ ああ言えばこう言う？
What's my treasure? When I don't plan to throw it away?
パクっとしたいわ
I want to snap it up!
端から端まで結ばれたいな
Bound tightly from end to end.
パクっとしたいわ
I want to snap it up!
指先と言葉で伝えたいな
Told through fingertips and words.
パクっとしたいわ
I want to snap it up!
ワガママかもしれないアンサーで
With a possibly selfish answer.
パクっとしたいわ
I want to snap it up!
どっちもどっちにしたいな
Wanting both sides to be equal.
音から意味まで結ばれたいな
Wanting to connect from sound to meaning.
パクっとしたいわ
I want to snap it up!
確かなことだけ見つからないや
Only certain things cannot be found.
パクっとしたいわ
I want to snap it up!
各々から繋がるアンサーで
With answers connecting from each of us.
パクっとしたいわ
I want to snap it up!
どっちもどっちにしたいな
Wanting both sides to be equal.
確かなことなどなくちゃじゃなくて
Not that there's nothing certain,
危険な願いも
even dangerous wishes,
止めないでその声が
don't stop, that voice
僕を連れて行くよ
will take me away.
愛に抱かれてギラギラ燃えてしまいたい
Embraced by love, I want to burn brilliantly!
daddy! daddy! do!
欲しいのさ
I want it all,
あなたのすべてが愛に抱かれギラギラ燃えてしまいたい
all of you, embraced by love, I want to burn!
可愛い kiss で
With a cute kiss,
1・2・3
1, 2, 3,
視線そらしてズルイよね
looking away, how sly of you.
火照り出すボクの気持ちもてあそぶみたいで
Playing with my flushed feelings like that.
愛嬌気取りなキスでは
With a coquettish kiss,
1・2・3 見せかけ空しー 別れ辛いよね
1, 2, 3, feigned emptiness—hard to part.
ホテルを出ず 僕の気持ち
Staying out of the hotel, my feelings
もてあそぶみたいで 追いかけちゃ
playing with them—to chase after you
ダメなのは分かってる でも無理さ
is no good, I know, but it's impossible!
一度踏み出せば戻れなくて
Once you step out, you can't go back,
仮面は脱ぎ捨てて いけない言葉で
tearing off the mask, with forbidden words
遊びがマジになる
play turns serious!
daddy! daddy! do!
欲しいのさ
I want it all,
あなたのすべてが
all of you!
だまされたら それでもいい
If I'm fooled, that's fine too,
もっと震わせて 魅せてくれ
make me shiver more, show me
僕だけに 笑顔の裏まで
only to me, even behind your smile!
愛に抱かれ ギラギラ燃えてしまいたい
Embraced by love, I want to burn!
ちょっぴり大人ぶって見せないの 二度と会えない人だから
Acting grown-up, because you're someone I'll never meet again.
後悔に暮れるなら 恋の火に焼かれたい
If drowning in regret, I want to burn in love's fire.
わざとでしょう 流し目が愛しさを刺激する そっと振り返る美しさに
On purpose, right? Sidelong glances spark affection, turning back...
心はつかまれて 呼吸が止まって
My heart is caught, breathing stops,
遊びがマジになる
and play turns serious!
daddy! daddy! do!
嫌いになれたらどんだけ楽だろう
How easy it would be if I could hate you,
危険な願いも 止めないでその声が
even dangerous wishes, don't stop, that voice
僕を連れて行くよ 愛に抱かれてギラギラ燃えてしまいたい
will take me! Embraced by love, I want to burn!
愛に抱かれてギラギラ燃えてしまいたい あなただけとゆく
Embraced by love, I want to burn, going with you alone!
DADDY! DADDY! DO!
欲しいのさ あなたのすべてが
I want all of you,
愛に抱かれ ギラギラ燃えてしまいたい
Embraced by love, I want to burn!
可愛げなkissで 1・2・3
With a cute kiss, 1, 2, 3...
目線そらしてズルいよね
Looking away, how sly of you.
火照り出すボクの気持ち もてあそぶみたいで
My feelings ignite, like a tease playing with fire.
追いかけちゃダメなのはわかってる でも無理さ
I know I shouldn't chase you, but I can't help it!
一度踏み出ば 戻れなくて
Once you step out, there's no turning back.
仮面は脱ぎ捨てて
Cast away your mask!
いけない言葉で 遊びがマジになる
Playing with forbidden words makes it serious.
DADDY! DADDY! DO!
欲しいのさ あなたのすべてが
I want all of you!
騙されたら それでもいい もっと震わせて
Even if I'm fooled, that's fine—just shake me more.
魅せてくれる 僕だけに 笑顔の裏まで
Show it to me, just for me, deep behind your smile.
愛に抱かれ ギラギラ燃えてしまいたい
Embraced by love, I want to burn!
躊躇などしない no no no
No hesitation, no, no, no!
二度と逢えない とりだから
Since we may never meet again,
後悔に暮れるのなら 恋の火に焼かれたい
If I'm left in regret, I want to burn in the fires of love.
わざとでしょう 流し目が愛しさを刺激する
It's intentional, that sideways glance stimulates love.
そっと振り返る 美しさに心はつかまれて
Gently looking back, my heart is captured by your beauty.
呼吸が止まって 遊びがマジになる
Breath stops, and this game becomes serious!
DADDY! DADDY! DO!
例えば今 君がその瞳 潤していたとしても
Even if your eyes were moist with tears right now,
呼ぶ声は もう聞こえない
I can no longer hear your voice calling out.
絵の具を溶かすように 君との日々は 記憶の中 滲んでく
Like dissolving paint, our days together fade deep into memory.
何かを求めれば 何かがこぼれ落ちてく
Whenever I reach for something, something else slips away—
そんなこの世界で
in this kind of world.
春の風を待つ あの花のように
Like that flower waiting for the spring breeze,
君という光があるのなら
if you are the light that exists for me,
巡り巡る運命を超えて
I will cross over the spinning wheel of fate
咲かせず 愛の花を 花束を
and make the flower of love, our bouquet, bloom.
願いが叶うのなら ふたりの世界 また生きてみたい
If wishes could come true, I'd want to live in our world once more.
あのキスから 芽吹く日々は
The days of budding from that kiss—
水色 花びらはもう香りを忘れ 君への想い 枯れていく
the aqua petals have forgotten their scent, and my feelings for you wither away.
散ってしまいそうな心に 覚え立ての愛の美しさを ねぇ 咲かせて
Take hold of my heart before it scatters, and let it bloom with the beauty of love.
春の風を待つ あの花のように
Like that flower waiting for the spring breeze,
飾らない心でいられたら
if only my heart could remain unadorned.
触れられなくても 想い煩っても
Even if we cannot touch, even if I struggle just to remember,
忘れないよ
I will never forget.
この恋をひとつずつ束ねいて
Gathering this love, one piece at a time—
君という光があるのなら
if you are the light that exists for me,
巡り巡る運命を超えて
I will cross over the spinning wheel of fate
咲かせる 愛の花を 花束を
and make the flower of love, our bouquet, bloom.
願いごとこののなら ふたりの世界 また生きてみたい
If I could dream, if I could live in a world just for the two of us,
あの日から 目吹く日々は
ever since that day, everyday is sprouting anew.
水色 花びらはもう香りを忘れ 君への想い 枯れていく
Petals of light have forgotten their scent, but my feelings for you remain.
散ってしまいそうな心に 覚え立ての愛の美しさを ねぇ 咲かせて
Take hold of my heart before it scatters, and let it bloom with the beauty of love.
春の風を待つ あの花のように
Like that flower waiting for the spring breeze,
飾らない心でいられたら
if only my heart could remain unadorned.
触れられなくても 想い煩っても
Even if we cannot touch, even if I struggle just to remember,
忘れないよ
I will never forget.
この恋をひとつずつ束ねいて
Gathering this love, one piece at a time—
君という光があるのなら
if you are the light that exists for me,
巡り巡る運命を超えて
I will cross over the spinning wheel of fate
咲かせる 愛の花を 花束を
and make the flower of love, our bouquet, bloom.
例えば 今 君 が その 瞳 濡らし て い た と し て も
Even if your eyes are moist with tears right now,
呼ぶ 声 は もう 聴こえ ない
I can no longer hear your voice calling me.
絵の具 を 溶かす よう に 君 と の 日々 は 記憶 の 中 滲ん で く
Like dissolving paint, our days together blur into my memories.
何 か を 求めれ ば 何 か が こぼれ落ち て くる
If I reach for something, something else spills away.
そんな この 世界 で
In a world like this...
春 の 風 を 待つ あの 花 の よう に
Like the flower waiting for the spring breeze,
誰か が 突然 に 始まっ た
Someone's story started all of a sudden,
デタラメ な シナリオ の 上 で
on a nonsensical scenario.
それ は 映画 の よう な まるで 映画 の よう な
It's like a movie, just like in the movies,
どこ に でも ある ストーリー
a story that can be found anywhere.
間違い だらけ の 道のり だ
It's a path full of mistakes,
丸付け られる の は いくつ だ
how many marks will I get?
何 が 良く ない の か どこ が 良く ない の か そこ まで 教え て くれ よ
What's wrong, what's no good—tell me all the way!
明け方 の 妄想 貴重 な 避難 行
Delusions at dawn, a precious escape,
勘違い の 英雄 ごっこ もう 渋滞 し て ん だ
playing the misunderstood hero, we're already gridlocked.
どう しよう も こう しよう も ない よ な こんな はず じゃ なかっ た よ な
There's nothing we can do, it wasn't supposed to be like this.
思え ば 思う ほど
The more I think about it,
いや これ じゃ ない ない 終わり は 悪い よう な 向い て ない ない 今 すぐ 辞め て しまう か
No, this isn't it. The ending feels bad, I'm not cut out for this—should I quit right now?
そりゃ ない ない いつ に なれ ば 僕 も 主役 に なれる ん だろう な
No way, when will I finally get to be the protagonist?
足り なく なる 度 笑っ たり
Laughing whenever we fall short,
増え た 荷物 数え て は 泣い たり
crying as we count our growing baggage.
期待 する ほど で も ない がっかり 責める こと すら でき ず 悩ん だり
Not expecting much, feeling disappointed, struggling without even being able to blame anyone.
爛々 と 輝く 街 の 灯り
The brightly shining city lights,
コレ じゃ ない ない 終わり は 悪い よう な 向い て ない ない 今 すぐ 辞め て しまえ ば
This isn't it, the ending feels bad, I'm not cut out for this—if I just quit right now,
でも 何 万 回 と 繰り返し て
repeating it tens of thousands of times,
走っ たり 来 たり し て しまう ん だ
running back and forth over and over.
明け方 の 覗き見 長 の 瞳孔 と 勘違い の 英雄 ごっこ
Peeking at dawn, dilated pupils and a misunderstood hero act.
もう 渋滞 し て ん だ どう しよう も こう しよう も ない よう な
We're already gridlocked, with nothing we can do about it.
あの 子 は 確か に あっ た ん だ 描き出し た もの が あっ た ん だ
That girl definitely had it, something she drew out was there.
いつの間にか 僕 は
Before I knew it, I...
誰か が 突然 に 始まっ た
Someone's story started all of a sudden,
デタラメ な シナリオ の 上 で
on a nonsensical scenario.
何か を 演じる の ? 誰 か を 演じる の ? そんな わけ が ない だろ
Acting as someone? Acting as somebody else? There's no way that's true.
全く これ じゃ ない ない 変わり は 悪い よう な 向い て ない ない 今 すぐ 辞め て しまう か
Not at all—this isn't it, the ending is bad, I'm not cut out for this, should I quit right now?
そりゃ ない ない いつ に なれ ば 僕 も 主役 に なれる ん だろう な
No way, when will I ever become the protagonist?
いつの日にか バイバイ 終わり は 来る から 白日 が さす 笑顔 で カーテンコール
Someday it'll be bye-bye, because an end will come—a curtain call with a bright, smiling face.
変え たい 未来 は ここ に あっ た 思う まま に 好き な よう に
The future I wanted to change was right here, just as I wished and liked.
これ は そう だ 最低 辺 から 駆け上がっ た
Yes, that's right—I ran all the way up from the very bottom.
映画 の よう な ストーリー
A story just like a movie.
世界 で 一番 僕 が 嫌い な の は 僕 だ と
When I realized that I'm the person I hate most in the world,
気付い た 時 から 黙り込ん で しまっ た
I fell silent from that moment on.
woh oh oh oh oh
世界で一番 僕が嫌いなのは
The person I hate the most in the world
僕だと気付いた時から 黙り込んでしまった
is myself; ever since I realized that, I've stayed silent.
友達なんとは 欲しいと思わなかったし
I never thought about wanting friends,
みんなに紛れて 何でも迎った
blending in with everyone and just going along with things.
君を好きになった それだけのことでも
Falling in love with you—even with just that,
全てがひっくり返って キラキラし始めた
everything turned upside down and started to sparkle.
愛してこんなにも 力があるのかな
Does love really have this much power?
僕らは生まれ変わったんだ 好きになってく
We were reborn, falling in love.
woh oh oh oh oh
人は何歳から 大人と呼ばれてしまうのか？
At what age do people start being called adults?
自分のことさえも 理解できないまま
Without even being able to understand myself,
何もやりたいことなんかなかった僕でも
even someone like me who had nothing they wanted to do
君に会えるかもしれない 明日が楽しみだ
looks forward to tomorrow, because I might meet you.
誰かを好きになる やさしいことなのに
Falling in love with someone is such a tender thing,
運命的に出会いなきゃ 心は動かない
yet unless we meet by fate, my heart won't move.
この恋逃したら 青春は終わる
If I let this romance slip away, my youth will end.
僕は僕を嫌いじゃない 好きになってく
I don't hate myself anymore; I'm starting to love myself.
心で感じた
Feeling it in my heart,
願いの強さよ
the strength of my wish,
前しか見えない
looking straight ahead,
答えが欲しい
I want an answer.
君を好きになった それだけのことでも
Falling in love with you—even with just that,
全てがひっくり返って キラキラし始めた
everything turned upside down and started to sparkle.
愛してこんなにも 力があるのかな
Does love really have this much power?
僕らは生まれ変わったんだ 好きになってく
We were reborn, falling in love.
woh oh oh oh oh
人は何歳から 大人と呼ばれてしまうのか？
At what age do people start being called adults?
自分のことさえも 理解できないまま
Without even being able to understand myself,
何もやりたいことなんかなかった僕でも
even someone like me who had nothing they wanted to do
君に会えるかもしれない 明日が楽しみだ
looks forward to tomorrow, because I might meet you.
誰かを好きになる やさしいことなのに
Falling in love with someone is such a tender thing,
運命的に出会いなきゃ 心は動かない
yet unless we meet by fate, my heart won't move.
この恋逃したら 青春は終わる
If I let this romance slip away, my youth will end.
僕は僕を嫌いじゃない 好きになってく
I don't hate myself anymore; I'm starting to love myself.
woh oh oh oh oh
心で感じた
Feeling it in my heart,
願いの強さよ
the strength of my wish,
前しか見えない
looking straight ahead,
答えが欲しい
I want an answer.
君を好きになった それだけのことでも
Falling in love with you—even with just that,
全てがひっくり返って キラキラし始めた
everything turned upside down and started to sparkle.
愛してこんなにも 力があるのかな
Does love really have this much power?
僕らは生まれ変わったんだ 好きになってく
We were reborn, falling in love.
君を好きになった それだけのことでも
Falling in love with you—even with just that,
全てがひっくり返って キラキラし始めた
everything turned upside down and started to sparkle.
愛してこんなにも 力があるのかな
Does love really have this much power?
僕らは生まれ変わったんだ 好きになってく
We were reborn, falling in love.
woh oh oh oh oh
君を後悔させない 好きになってく
I won't let you regret it, falling in love.
好きになってく
Falling in love.
世界で一番 僕が嫌いなのは僕だと
The person I hate the most is myself,
気付いた時から 黙り込んでしまった
ever since I realized that, I've kept silent.
誰が袖に咲く幻花
Who is the phantom flower that blooms on the sleeve?
ただ そこに藍を落とした
I just dropped my dye over there.
派手に色を溶かす夜に
On a night when the colors dissolve gaudily,
銀朱の月を添えて
with the moon of silver vermillion.
転がるように風を切って
Cutting through the wind as if rolling,
呟く強くなった
growing stronger with every stumble.
光も痛みも怒りも全部抱きしめれば
Embracing all the light, pain, and anger,
選ばれなければ 選べばいい
if not chosen, then choose.
声よ どろけ 夜のその向こうへ
Let your voice roar beyond the night,
涙で滲んでた
soaked with tears.
あんなに遠くの景色まで 響き渡れ
Let it reverberate across the distant scenery.
何を奏でて? 誰に届けたくて?
What do I want to play? Who do I want to reach?
不確かなままでいい
It's okay to remain uncertain.
どんなに暗い感情も
No matter how dark the emotions,
どんなに長い葛藤も
no matter how long the struggle,
歌と散れ 残響
sing and scatter, reverberation.
ただひとり舞う千夜
A thousand nights of dancing alone,
たがえないタイを結べば
if I tie the same sash,
派な色も負かすように
as if to defeat the gaudy colors,
銀朱の過去こそ哀れ
the crimson past is truly pitiful.
この先 どんな辛い時も
From now on, no matter how hard times get,
口先よりも胸を張って
proudly put your heart on the line rather than just words,
抱いた夢のあかりを全部たどるだけ
and follow all the lights of the dreams you held.
逃げだすためここまで来たんじゃないだろ?
We didn't come all this way just to run away, right?
選ばれなければ 選べばいい
If not chosen, then choose.
声をからして 燃える花のように
With a voice hoarse like a burning flower,
闇間を照らしたら
lighting up the darkness,
曖昧過ぎる正解も譜面にして
turn even overly vague answers into a musical score,
夜を数えて朝を描くような
like counting the nights and painting the morning,
鮮やかな音を鳴らす
ringing out vivid sounds.
どんなに深い後悔も
No matter how deep the regrets,
どんなに高い限界も
no matter how high the limits,
掻き消して 残響
scratch them out, reverberation.
ひたむきな夢の灯を全部たどるだけ
Just following all halos of earnest dreams.
逃げだすためここまで来たんじゃないだろ?
We didn't come all this way just to run away, right?
声をからして 燃える花のように
With a voice hoarse like a burning flower,
闇間を照らしたら
lighting up the darkness,
曖昧過ぎる世界も 不明にして
turning even overly vague worlds into uncertainty,
夜を数えて 朝を描くような
like counting the nights and painting the morning,
鮮やかな目を鳴らす
ringing out vivid eyes.
どんなに深い後悔も
No matter how deep the regrets,
どんなに高い限界も
no matter how high the limits,
掻き消して 残響
scratch them out, reverberation.
半端なら K.O.
Half-ass deserves a K.O.
ふわふわしたいならどうぞ
So be it, if you want to be light-hearted.
開演準備しちゃおうか
Shall we get ready for the show?
泣いてても笑ってても愛してね
Whether crying or laughing, please love me.
ほら Say No
Come on, say no,
低音響かせろ
and let the bass resonate.
なんかなくってつまんないこともあるでしょう
There must be times when nothing feels boring, right?
ロンリー論理のノート ハンディー本気脱走
Lonely logic notes, a handy serious escape.
やんなちゃって泥に Bad ご法度だろうが 浸れ堕ちて
Even if it's a bad taboo to fall into the mud, drown and fall.
そろそろ行こうか もっと頑張って アガるまでもっと頑張って
It's about time to go, work harder until you get excited.
繋がろうひとりよりふたり 増えたら安心 心配ないや
Let's connect, one plus one, more people means relief, no worries.
Alright 任せて Don't mind 波あり難題
Alright, leave it to me, don't mind troubles with waves.
みんなで乗っかちゃえば 案外さくっと行いそうね
If we all ride along, it might surprisingly go smoothly.
半端なら K.O.
Half-ass deserves a K.O.
ふわふわしたいならどうぞ
So be it, if you want to be light-hearted.
開演準備しちゃおうか
Shall we get ready for the show?
泣いてても笑ってても愛してね
Whether crying or laughing, please love me.
ほら Say No
Come on, say no,
低音響かせろ
and let the bass resonate.
今宵は暗転パーティー
Tonight is a blackout party.
Woah 踊りだせ 踊りだせ
Woah, dance, dance,
孤独は殺菌
loneliness is sanitized,
満員御礼
full house, thank you.
Woah 痛みまで おシェアで
Woah, sharing even the pain,
ここらでバイバイ let go
saying bye-bye right here, let go.
チョットでいいから 見せてくれないか
Show me for just a little bit, won't you?
お前のセクシーフェルモンで オレ メロメロ
With your sexy pheromone, I'm totally infatuated.
AHふれあいそう でも イケナイの!
Ah, it seems like we might touch, but no, you mustn't!
徐々に高鳴る鼓動 とめられないわ
Gradually quickening heartbeat, I can't stop it.
交わす言葉の 記憶遠く
The memories of our exchanged words are far away.
口元の動きに揺られ動く
Swaying with the movement of your lips,
濡れた髪を撫でた そして AH?
I stroked your damp hair, and then AH?
別に興味ない No No
I don't care at all, no no,
特に係わりない No No
It has nothing to do with me, no no.
差し込んで絶好調へ
Plunging right into top form!
ノイズを奏でて プルプルプルプルイエッ ブラッ詰まって 夜空へイェイェ
Playing noise, plip-plip-plip-plip-yeah...
泣いていこう
Let's cry!
赤い糸なんて絵空事
Even if red threads are just an illusion,
でも下心でさえ信じたいの
I want to believe even in ulterior motives.
俺は正しい キミも正しい
I'm right, you're right.
とにかくもう左右されないぜ
Anyway, I won't be swayed by anything anymore.
騙し騙され胸うずく
Deceiving and being deceived, my chest throbs.
下手な芝居が より盛り上げる夜
A clumsy act makes the night even more exciting.
息が耳に触れた二人 AH
The two of us with our breath touching our ears, AH.
ABC続かない そんなんじゃダメじゃない
ABC doesn't continue, if it's like that it's no good, right?
だって ココロの奥は違うんじゃない?
Because deep down in our hearts, isn't that different?
オレの青春 そんなもんじゃない
My youth isn't something like that.
熱く奥で果てたいよ
I want to burn out passionately deep inside.
きっと キミじゃなきゃ やだよ
Surely it has to be you, no one else!
オレはイケナイ太陽
I am the forbidden sun!
意外に普通の年越しに負けたな
Losing to a normal New Year's eve is lame.
そうだ!
That's right!
年越しの瞬間みんなでジャンプしよう!
Let's all jump at the moment of the New Year!
いや普通 てかみんな爪痕残すの無理くね?
"Normal"? Besides, isn't it impossible for everyone to leave their mark?
あと3分で年越し変わるし
And there's only 3 minutes left until the New Year!
そんなこともあるか と用意してるやん!
As if that would happen—we've prepared for it!
神薬は超エクセレント! これよりだけで世界征服できるよ!
With just this, you can conquer the world!
よし、その薬を使って先輩が年越しくるんだ!
We'll use that drug to make the seniors come over!
呼んで呼んで呼んで呼んで呼んで呼んで呼んで...
Call them, call them, call them...
いい加減諦めろ!
Give it a break already!
まだまだ! 2時まで年越しが良い! 2時丸23はださんさいとか言うな!
Don't say things like "Marusan-sai" past 2 o'clock!
来年はお前らの番なんだから!
Next year is your turn!
何やってんですか?
What are you doing?
何やってると思う?
What do you think we're doing?
問題
Question:
これはいつの初日の出でしょーか?
When was this first sunrise of the year?
わかるか!
How should I know?!
からししんってことは比較的最近。
Judging from the mustard, it's relatively recent.
まじめ。
Serious.
一昨年ですね?
It was the year before last, right?
正解!
Correct!
へえ、なるほどねえ。
Oh, I see.
すっげえパワー!
Such incredible power!
ほうぎと... これに握られたら絶対に折れるや...
If you're gripped by this, it'll definitely snap...
大丈夫すか?
Are you okay?
寝返れないよ。
I can't roll over.
なんだとこ...
What is thi...
え,そんなとこ... はげしく怒られちゃう?
Will we get chewed out furiously?
怒らせないと いけないのか?
Do we have to make them angry?
地球!
Earth!
フレア!
Flare!
ノエル!
Noel!
船長を一人にしな...
Don't leave the captain all alone...
呼ばないでよ!
Don't call me!
なんで追いかけてくるの? なんておっかけてよ!
Why are you chasing us?!
世の方の年越し急うから!
Because we're rushing through the world's New Year!
あれは我々のカルマが呼び寄せた案件で
That was a case summoned by our karma—
夜あるの?
Is there a night?
なんて? なんでですか?
What? Why is that?
ちょっとでも東に行って、みんなより早く年を越す!
Go even slightly east and surpass everyone in ringing in the New Year!
それがはーちゃまの病気じゃ!
That is Haachama's disease!
あのまま行けばジムシャつか。
If we keep going, we'll reach the gym.
ギブギブギブギブ!
Give, give, give, give!
ファイトファイト!
Fight, fight!
ノージャンプにゃう!
No-jump meow!
まだやれるだろ!
You can still do it!
レフェリー! レフェリー!
Referee! Referee!
止めなくていいのかな...
Should we stop them...?
反省したか?
Have you reflected on this?
生きるためには頭数減らさねぇとな。
To survive, we've got to reduce our numbers.
お前が出てけ!
You get out!
こんなんですか?
Is it like this?
こんなんです!
It's like this!
諦めがしっかりしないと全滅だ!
If we don't give up properly, it's total annihilation!
こんなんですか? こんなんです!
Is it like this? It's like this!
これで揃ったな。
Everyone's here now.
すみません、お付き合いいただいて。
Sorry to drag you along with this.
2023まで 16 15 14 13...
Counting down to 2023: 16, 15, 14, 13...
それじゃあ行きますね!
Well then, let's go!
ゼロ! / HAPPY NEW YEAR!
HAPPY NEW YEAR!
ヤッホー! こんなことしていいんでござるか?
Yahoo! Is it really okay to do something like this?
怒られるじゃ済まないね。
Getting scolded is the least of our worries.
映ってく先輩たちかわいい!
The seniors on screen are so cute!
ワーッ!
Waaah!
笑顔ならどんなどんな輝きの中でも強い煌めき
No matter what kind of smile, it's a bright sparkle
君に届いているかな 一ミリでも伝われば
Is it reaching you? Even if just by a millimeter,
おちゃじちゃれんびん全力アクセルじゃんばる君へ
Charge, challenge, full throttle, straight to you!
一番乗りのスマイルを送る座るちゃんねる
Sending the first-place smile to the Subaru Channel!
Ring-Dong Ring-Dong 鼓動がBeat it
Ring-Dong Ring-Dong, my heartbeat is beat it
期待もHeat up 感じてJoy! Joy! もっとエンジョイ
Expectations heat up, feeling Joy! Joy! Enjoy more!
フィジカルStreaming
Physical streaming,
上々気分も つよしよHomeRun
High spirits too, strong HomeRun!
団長 真の才能 ヒエラルKeyword
Leader's true talent, the hierarchical keyword,
見せつけてあげる Lovely Party
I'll show you a lovely party!
ぴゅるるーんるん ぴゅるるーんるん
Pyuru-ru-n-run, Pyuru-ru-n-run,
巻き起こす言霊Typhoon
Stirring up a kotodama typhoon!
もっと Happy トコトコトコ届きちゃうよ
More Happy, step-step-stepping right to you!
飛び交うカメラのシャッターチャンス見届けて飛び越えて
Capturing the shutter chance of flying cameras, leaping over,
誰も見たことない世界に みんなで行こうよ！
Let's all go together to a world nobody has ever seen!
君とスマヤンGO 踏み出せモンガチンコ
Smile & GO with you, step forward, mongachinko!
君とスマヤンGO はじけけたモンガチンコ
Smile & GO with you, bursting out mongachinko!
ここに笑顔で集まれば 最高潮でしょ
If we gather here with smiles, it's at its peak, right?
僕とスマヤンGO モテモテ作戦
Smile & GO with me, the popular strategy,
僕とスマヤンGO 遊びまくろうだって
Smile & GO with me, let's play to our heart's content,
この道中が大切な宝物だから
Because this journey is an important treasure.
Smile & Go!
大好きな僕を
The me you love,
君が好きな僕を ちゃんと あまりに見せたいの
The me you love, I want to show you properly!
おっとっと びっくりするほどできないじゃん
Whoa-whoa, I can't even do it to a surprising degree,
間違って悩んでばっかりじゃん
Just making mistakes and worrying constantly.
けど君に見つけてほしくて 出会えたならハッピー
I want you to find me, so if we meet, it's happy!
わおわお歌うぜ 歌え歌え愛して尻尾振って
Wao-Wao, singing away! Sing, sing, love me, wag your tail!
わおわお歌うぜ 駄目な僕をどうか覚えておいて
Wao-Wao, singing away! Please remember useless old me,
もう君の心 チクッとしちゃえ
Pierce right through your heart!
大賛成やだったら コーチングくらえ
If you don't like it, take some coaching!
こんな場所なんてさ 気分で作らなくちゃ
A place like this, we gotta make it on a whim!
これぞ清く正しくラッタッタ トータ
This is purely, righteously rattatta, ta-ta!
ありがた迷惑だから ランダムレインボー
It's unwanted kindness, so random rainbow!
世界平和は 視線奪えば
World peace is stealing gazes,
毎日大惨敗 大成功乱されたら
Daily major routs, if our grand success is disturbed,
笑えないじゃうんだ 笑え
We can't laugh, hey, laugh!
ペッコラダンスあるんだか
Is there a Pekora dance?
ペッコラダンスなんてちゃっかりマイ
A Pekora dance, quite slyly my...
ペッコラダンスあるんだか
Is there a Pekora dance?
ペッコラダンスナンナンナンナンヤー
Pekora dance, na-na-na-na-yeah!
ぶっちゃけ先っちょ捕まえられたくない
Honestly, I don't want you catching the tip,
よそうがなかっちゃトレジャー
Otherwise it's not a treasure,
Maybe tasting me 私の甘さが欲しいんでしょ
Maybe tasting me, you want my sweetness, right?
秘密の鍵を 優しく刺して
Gently insert the secret key,
宝庫の扉マジで早く開けて じれったい貴方の手
Quickly open the vault door for real, your impatient hands,
海図にこぼす甘いため息のTease
Spilling sweet sighs of tease onto the nautical chart.
純紅のバラが しおれる前に WE WILL SAIL THE SEVEN SEAS
Before the crimson roses wither, WE WILL SAIL THE SEVEN SEAS
未来を咲かせよ 次世代愛して高まって
Make the future bloom, love the next generation, soaring high,
溜まったMPパワーはなくて
With no accumulated MP power left,
黒術指定の刻に集えよ 闇に奮えケルベロス
Gather at the dark arts. Tremble in the darkness, Cerberus!
切に響く言葉は ブチギレ発狂パラダイス
Words echoing sharply, a snapping, raving paradise.
キラリ心奥そこまで届け これからも私の元で
Sparkling, reaching deep into the heart, stay with me,
下した力放て いやん待ってあっち向いて
Release the commanded power—wait, look the other way!
昔話で覚えた呪文唱えて
Reciting the spell I learned from fairy tales,
何かが起きるかも？と期待して
Hoping something might happen?
くたびれた 内緒だよ
It's a secret, you know,
口笛吹いて誤魔化すの
whistling to brush it off.
溢れ出す光
Overflowing light...
差し出したこの手が触れた瞬間
the moment this extended hand touched.
運命を超えて
Transcending fate,
どこまでも続いていく道のその先も
let's keep walking down this endless road.
笑って歩いて行こう
Smiling all the way,
答えなんてないなら 全部答えにして
if there's no answer, let's make it all the answer.
“楽しい”だけ感じたい
I only want to feel joy.
いつも貴方の背中見てた
I always looked at your back,
今日くらい私に任せて欲しい
so today, please let me take the lead.
軽やかなステップで
With light steps,
虹の上でも歩けちゃいそうさfantasy
we could walk even on a rainbow, fantasy!
すぐに飛んで行くよ
I'll fly right away.
もっと もっと 特別になってもらいたいの
I want you to make me feel extra special.
いつでもそう 私は
Whenever, I am always like this.
ご機嫌斜めにそっぽなんて向かせないわ
I won't let you look away in a bad mood!
ねぇ ほら夢中にしちゃうわ
Hey, look, I'll have you completely hooked.
もう少しずつ好きがいいの
I want you to fall for me little by little.
心も体も染まっていく
My heart and body are dyeing in your colors.
側に来てこっち向いてよ
Come closer and look at me.
もう離さないから
I'm never letting you go.
絶対に 約束だよ
Definitely, it's a promise!
愛してちょうだいもっと
Please love me even more,
だって ぼくは 星だから
because I am a star.
stellar stellar きっと きみも気付いていた
Stellar stellar, I'm sure you already noticed.
ざわざわ街のざわめきなんてはねのけっ放けの考え
Shaking off the bustling noise of the city,
今夜音楽はずっとずっとやまない
tonight, the music will never stop.
ざわざわ街のざわめきなんてはねのけっ放けの世界宇宙の中で
Shaking off the noise, deep in the cosmic universe,
今夜音楽はきっときっとやまない
tonight, the music will surely never stop.
そんなぼくがずっと泣きたかったのは
The reason someone like me wanted to cry,
まっくしろシンデレラじゃないさ
wasn't because I'm a Cinderella.
向こうに行く王子様じゃないさ
Not the prince going to the other side,
すくいにいくヒーローだ
but the hero going to save you!
そんなぼくがずっと泣きたかったのは
The reason someone like me wanted to cry,
まっくしろシンデレラじゃないさ
wasn't because I'm a Cinderella.
すてら、すてら
Stellar, stellar...
あけましておめでとうございます！
Happy New Year!
大胆不敵にハイカラ革命
Audacious and dauntless, high-collar revolution,
磊々落々反戦国家
thunderous and untamed, anti-war state.
日ノ丸印の二輪車転がし
Rolling the motorcycle with the rising sun emblem,
悪霊退散ICBM
exorcising evil spirits, ICBM!
環状線を走り抜けて 東奔西走なんのその
Running through the loop line, running east and west,
少年少女戦国無双 浮世の随に
youth Sengoku Musou, following the floating world.
千本桜 夜に紛れ 君の声も届かないよ
Senbonzakura, lost in the night, your voice won't reach.
此処は宴 鋼の檻 その断頭台で見下ろして
This is a banquet, a cage of steel, look down from the guillotine.
三千世界 常世之闇 嘆く唄も聴こえないよ
Three thousand worlds, eternal darkness, even lamenting songs cannot be heard.
青藍の空 遥か彼方 その光線銃で打ち抜いて
Far beyond the deep blue sky, shoot through with that ray gun.
百戦錬磨の見た目は将校
A veteran's appearance is that of an officer.
いったりきたりの花魁道中
The courtesan's procession going back and forth,
アイツもコイツも皆で集まれ
everyone gather here, friend and foe alike!
聖者の行進 わんっ つー さん しっ
The procession of saints, one, two, three, four!
禅定門を潜り抜けて 安楽浄土厄払い
Passing through the Zen gate, purifying souls and warding off evil.
きっと終幕は大団円 拍手の間間に
Surely the finale is a grand ending, amidst the applause.
千本桜 夜に紛れ 君の声も届かないよ
Senbonzakura, lost in the night, your voice won't reach.
此処は宴 鋼の檻 その断頭台で見下ろして
This is a banquet, a cage of steel, look down from the guillotine.
大胆不敵にハイカラ革命
Fearless and bold, a high-collar revolution
磊々落々反戦国家
Open-minded and candid, an anti-war nation
日の丸印の二輪車転がし
Riding bicycles marked with the rising sun
悪霊退散 ICBM
Exorcising evil spirits with ICBMs
環状線を走り抜けてきて
Running right through the loop line
東奔西走なんのその
Running east and west, thinking nothing of it
少年少女戦国無双
Boys and girls unmatched in the warring states
浮世の随に
As the floating world goes
千本桜 夜ニ紛レ
A thousand cherry blossoms, lost in the night
君ノ声モ届カナイヨ
Even your voice cannot reach me anymore
此処は宴鋼の檻
This place is a banquet in a cage of steel
その断頭台で見下ろして
Look down from that guillotine
三千世界 常世之闇
Three thousand worlds, the darkness of eternity
嘆ク唄モ聞コエナイヨ
Even songs of lament cannot be heard
青藍の空遥か彼方
Far beyond the azure sky
その光線銃で打ち抜いて
Shoot through it with that ray gun
百戦錬磨の見た目は将軍
A general in appearance, honed by a hundred battles
いったりきたりの花魁道中
An oiran procession going back and forth
アイツもコイツも皆で集まれ
Everyone gathering together, friend and foe alike
聖者の行進 わんっ つー さん しっ
The march of saints, one, two, three, four!
禅定門を潜り抜け
Slipping through the zen-jō gate
安楽浄土厄払い
Dispelling misfortune in the pure land of bliss
きっと終幕は大団円
Surely the finale will be a grand conclusion
拍手の合間に
Amidst the sound of applause
千本桜 夜ニ紛レ
A thousand cherry blossoms, lost in the night
君ノ声モ届カナイヨ
Even your voice cannot reach me anymore
此処は宴鋼の檻
This place is a banquet in a cage of steel
その断頭台で見下ろして
Look down from that guillotine
三千世界 常世之闇
Three thousand worlds, the darkness of eternity
嘆ク唄モ聞コエナイヨ
Even songs of lament cannot be heard
希望の丘遥か彼方
Far beyond the hill of hope
その閃光弾を打ち上げろ
Launch that signal flare high
環状線を走り抜けてきて
Running right through the loop line
東奔西走なんのその
Running east and west, thinking nothing of it
少年少女戦国無双
Boys and girls unmatched in the warring states
浮世の随に
As the floating world goes
千本桜 夜ニ紛レ
A thousand cherry blossoms, lost in the night
君ノ声モ届カナイヨ
Even your voice cannot reach me anymore
此処は宴鋼の檻
This place is a banquet in a cage of steel
その断頭台を飛び降りて
Jumping down from that guillotine
千本桜 夜ニ紛レ
A thousand cherry blossoms, lost in the night
君が歌い僕は踊る
You sing and I dance
此処は宴鋼の檻
This place is a banquet in a cage of steel
さあ光線銃を撃ちまくれ
Now, fire your ray gun everywhere!
改めて、あけまして、おめでとうございます！
Once again, Happy New Year!
お正月ということで、振袖で登場しちゃいました！いかがですか、振袖？
Since it's New Year's, I appeared in a furisode! How do you like my furisode?
昨年の、新年の新聞でね、来ていた着物になります。
This is the kimono I wore in last year's New Year's newspaper.
なんかこうやって実際に着物着てみると、ちょっと、なんか、右、身がね、引き締まる思いですね。
Wearing an actual kimono like this really makes me feel a bit more disciplined and focused.
そして、ステージも見てください！こんなに豪華なステージがあるんですよ！あっち見に行きましょう、あっち。
And please look at the stage! There's such a gorgeous stage here! Let's go check over there, over there.
こちらには、今年がね、ウサギ年ということで、ウサギのね、なんか飛んでるウサギさんがいたりとか、
Over here, since this year is the Year of the Rabbit, there are flying rabbits and...
後ろのね、金屏風には富士山が描いてあったりとか、あとは綺麗な花、あと門松！
On the gold folding screen in the back, Mount Fuji is painted, plus beautiful flowers and kadomatsu!
門松はね、あっち側にもあるんですよ。見事に立派な木もありますね。こんな感じで、もう「お正月おめでとうね」っていう感じのステージになってます。
There are kadomatsu on the other side too. There are also splendid, magnificent trees. It's a stage that really gives off a 'Happy New Year' vibe.
上にはね、「迎春」って書いてあるんだよ。ほら！
Up top, it says 'Welcoming Spring'. Look!
みんなも、あ、だるま？だるまのおウサギさんもいる、かわいい！素敵なね、お正月のステージ、ありがとうございます！
Everyone, oh, a daruma? There's a daruma rabbit too, so cute! Thank you for this wonderful New Year's stage!
そして、この、およ……お洋服ではないですけど、この格好、覚えてますか？こういう感じで新聞に乗っておりました。
And do you remember this outfit... well, not clothes, but this look? I appeared in the newspaper looking like this.
あんきもも、あんきもも今とっても喜んでるよ。僕もお正月にでれたよって喜んでる。
Ankimo, Ankimo is also super happy right now. He's saying, "I got to appear for New Year's too," and he's so happy.
そして、この、後ろの方をね、ちょっと見てみましょうか。帯がね、こういう感じで、すごくちょっとね、大人っぽいものになっていたりとか、がらまね、やっぱお花になっていて、下のほうから、だんだん...
And let's take a look at the back. The obi is styled like this, very mature, and the pattern is flowers, and from the bottom, gradually...
なんとなんか明るくなっていくような色合いになってるんです。
Everything is becoming brighter and more colorful.
髪飾りね、とっても可愛くて。
The hair accessories are really cute!
なんだかこんなね、振り袖で1月1日を迎えられてとても嬉しく思っています。
I'm so happy to be able to welcome January 1st with such wide sleeves!
そしてホロライブは今年5周年をむかえています。
And Hololive is celebrating its 5th anniversary this year.
5年前はね、まさか振り袖を着れるようになるとは思わず、来たことあるんですけど、袖がなかったみたいな。
5 years ago, I never thought I'd be able to wear sleeves like this, but I didn't have sleeves!
袖のない振り袖だったのかなね、5年たってちゃんと振り袖をこうやって切れるようになったり、
It's been 5 years, and I've finally learned to properly wear sleeves!
そしてね、仲間がたくさん増えてこんなにね、素敵なスタッフさんたちと素敵な番組を作れるようになりました。
And we've got so many new friends, wonderful staff, and wonderful programs!
本当にそれはみなさんの応援があるからだなと思います。
I really think that's thanks to everyone's support.
これからも私たちは頑張っていくので今年もホロライブをよろしくお願いします。
We're going to keep doing our best, so please continue to support Hololive this year!
さてさて、
Now, now!
新年ということで嬉しいお知らせもいっぱいしていけたらいいなと思いますよ！
I hope we can share lots of happy New Year news with you!
では、いきますね。
So, let's get started!
まずは、こちら！
First is this one!
今年はうさぎ年ということで、ぺこらちゃんが何やらよからぬことを考えているみたい。
This year is the Year of the Rabbit, and Pekora-chan seems to be planning something unexpected...
その名も、#全人類うさぎ化計画！
Its name is the #AllHumanityRabbitizationProject!
いったい何がね、始まるんだろう。
What on earth is going to happen?
こちらは本日1月1日夜19時からホロライブ公式チャンネルにて配信予定です。
This will be broadcasted today, January 1st, starting at 7:00 PM on the official Hololive channel!
みんな、19時の予定はあけといてねよ！
Everyone, make sure to clear your schedule for 7:00 PM!
続いては、こちら！
Next is this!
1月13日金曜日、ピクシブ様とホロライブクリエイターコンテスト2023を開催します！
The "Hololive Creator Contest 2023" hosted by Pixiv will be held starting January 13th, Friday!
ホロライブをテーマにしたイラスト、水着衣装デザイン、シナリオの3点をクリエイターの皆様に約1ヶ月募集させていただきます。
We're looking for illustrations, swimsuit designs, and scenario scripts from creators for about a month!
詳細は1月13日の公式ツイートをご確認ください。
For details, please check the official tweet on January 13th!
続いては、こちら！
Next is this!
過去ホロライブメンバーが出演したホロライブアイドルプロジェクトファーストライブブルームが現在アベマで配信中です。
The 1st live concert of the Hololive Idol Project, "Bloom,", featuring past Hololive members, is currently streaming on ABEMA!
ブルームを見てくれた人も見たことがない人もこの機会にぜひチェックしてみてください。
Whether you've watched Bloom before or never have, please take this opportunity to check it out!
詳細はアベマのホームページで検索してみてね。
Details can be found on the ABEMA homepage!
続いては、こちら！
Next is this!
明日1月2日にみこちのお正月衣装お披露目もあるよ！
Tomorrow, January 2nd, at 20:00, Miko-chi's New Year outfit reveal is coming up!
どうやら色んな企画を用意してるみたいだから、みんなチェックしてみてね！
It looks like she's got all sorts of plans in store, so everyone be sure to check it out!
そしてそして、続いては、こちら！
And then, next is this!
星街すいせいセカンドアルバムSPECTER1月25日水曜日発売決定！おめでとう！
Hoshimachi Suisei's 2nd album, "SPECTER", will be released on Wednesday, January 25th! Congratulations!
セカンドアルバムとなる今作では、Ayase、じん、キタニタツヤやナナホシ管弦楽団だ豪華クリエイター陣が書き下ろした全11曲を収録した作品となっています。現在予約受付中！
This second album features all 11 tracks written by gorgeous creators like Ayase, Jin, Tatsuya Kitani, and Nano.Hoshi Gangdan! Reservations are open now!
さらに星街すいせいセカンドソロライブSHOUTiNCRISIS2023年1月28日土曜日に東京ガーデンシアターにて開催！
Furthermore, Hoshimachi Suisei's 2nd Solo Live "Shout in Crisis" will be held on Saturday, January 28, 2023, at Tokyo Garden Theater!
現在SPWNにて配信チケット発売中！
Ticket sales on SPWN are live right now!
詳しくは各種公式サイトをご確認ください。
Check the official website for more details!
そして、続いては、こちら！
And then, next is...
今年も常闇トワさん主催のホロお正月カップを開催します！
This year, we are holding the "Holo New Year Cup 2023" hosted by Tokoyami Towa-san!
今年の最強は誰の手に！みんな楽しみだね！
Whose hands will the strongest title go to this year? Everyone, get excited!
そして雑魚杯の優勝者は！
And the winner of the losers' bracket...
ぜひ皆さんチェックしてくださいね！
Please make sure to check it out, everyone!
そしてそしてたくさんの告知もいよいよ最後です。
And with that, we're finally at our last announcement!
最後は、こちら！
The last one is this!
1月5日お昼頃から友人Aちゃんと春先のどかちゃんのホロライブスタッフコンビで年末年始の振り返り配信を実施します。
On January 5th around noon, A-chan and Nodoka Harusaki will host a look-back stream on the Hololive staff channel covering the tumultuous New Year period!
ゆくホロくるホロやカウントダウンライブなどなどスタッフ視点での裏話も
We'll be sharing behind-the-scenes staff stories about the countdown live, the count-up live, and more!
年末年始の情報はこの放送でばっちりおさえちゃいましょう！
Let's wrap up all the info from the New Year right here!
詳細は2人のTwitterを見てね！
Check both of their Twitter accounts for details!
あけまして おめでとうございます！
Happy New Year!
ホロライブプロダクションを どうぞ よろしくお願いします！
Please enjoy Hololive Production!